The world is amidst the Great Pirate Era.
In pursuit of fame, fortune and power,
ambitious souls take to the sea.
For pirates, it's an era that is like a dream.
But among them, there are those
who seek only to plunder...
And for the powerless, it means
an age of relentless oppression.
Even the Navy, working at the behest of the
World Government, can not help everyone...
So who can the oppressed turn to?
On what can they pin
their hopes for salvation?
We're in a real fix...
No one's looking out for folks like us.
I cry all the time lately...
Everyone agrees:
the Navy is bad, but what's worse is...
I'm hungry!
What did you expect?
The pirates took everything.
That's right! It's the pirates' fault!
Because of them being so greedy...
No one gets to have fun anymore!
Do you understand what we're going through?
Please. We're suffering...
You're the only one.
The only one who can help...!
--Please.
--You can fix this...
--I'm begging you.
--You're only only hope!
Please!
I know. I know, everyone.
I'm going to create a new age
where you can all be happy.
This is one huge crowd.
Well, the famous Uta is performing live
in front of a crowd for the first time!
She's only done stuff over Video
Transponder Snails until now!
Uta in person!
And in such an awesome place!
I'm... I'm so...!
There's even merfolk around.
Should be quite a show.
But why are we dressed like this?
Showing up in costume to help hype up
her first show gets you these!
That's why?
I'm looking forward to it.
She's the entire world's
sweetheart, at this point.
Is this chick really that big a deal?
As odd as it might sound coming from
Soul King, her voice is otherworldly.
U! T! A! Uta-chan!
What a loser.
Hey, crap swordsman! Say that again
and I'll cook you up nice and juicy!
I'd like to see you try, Twirly Brow.
Here we go!
Hey! The show's starting, Luffy!
We can choose the way of our future
Try a brand new path...
If I change the world
Say goodbye to everyone
who stands against us
No one has the power to stop a change
that comes through music
No, you can't stop magic
Close your eyes and you can see
the future before you
Every note I sing is bringin' you
closer to your purpose
Once you're there don't let go
You wanna play a real game,
unfurl the chain
Melody strung out like we're
walkin' on a tight rope
Don't wanna cry,
don't wanna try, wanna forget
Just let me live inside a dreamland
Wanna be free!
And let a brand new era dawn
I know that we can
Create a new world!
We can choose the way of our future
Try a brand new path...
If I change the world
If I change the world...
This boundless music brings transformation
Messages in song
Reach even further
This dream will come true
I believe in you
Say goodbye to everything
that's weighing you down
Transcend beyond reality
to colorful worlds of music
We need to keep on rising
Close your eyes and take my hand
we're runnin' together
We don't have to live like this,
I know we can all do better
I sing for liberation
You wanna play a real game,
unfurl the chain
Melody lighting up the path to new horizons
Don't wanna cry,
don't wanna try, wanna forget
Just let me live inside a dreamland
Wanna be free!
And let a brand new era dawn
I know that we can
Create a new world!
We can choose the way of our future
Try a brand new path
If I change the world...
This boundless music brings transformation
Messages in song
Reach even further
A New Genesis
It's great to finally meet you all! I'm Uta!
Sorry... this is a lot to take in.
Let's all have a great time today!
You boys ready?
Yeah.
Snatch up a star like her
and we'll be rich and famous!
Too bad for you, Uta!
U-T-A! U-T-A! U-T-A!
Whoa, Luffy!
Is this guy after Uta, too?
Hey, I was right!
Uta! You're Uta, aren't you?!
It's me, remember?!
Me?
Wait... Luffy?!
It's been a real long time, Uta!
Luffy!
Wha--?!
--Wait, that straw hat...
--It can't be!
--The fifth Emperor?!
No way. Uta wouldn't be friends with a pirate!
Luffy knows Uta?
Dammit! He could've introduced us, then!
Why exactly are you so friendly
with Princess Uta--?
Huh?!
'Cause she's Shanks' daughter!
When he says Shanks...
That's one of the Four Emperors.
A major bad guy!
I remember a long time ago...
Yeah. He's the one who attacked Elegia!
Uta...
I had thought it was odd
that Elegia was the venue...
Because of the old legend?
Right. But this adds a whole new wrinkle to it.
Who're you guys?
So "Red-Haired" Shanks of the Four
Emperors has a daughter?
If it's true, that'd make you
his biggest weakness...
Red-Haired's baby girl!
We fork you over to one the big-name
pirate crews and we'll make a huge profit!
So there you have it.
Sorry, but this concert is canceled!
Heat Beating!
We'll be taking the girl!
It's you...
--Branch!
--Branch?
My name is Brulee! With the Big Mom Pirates!
What about the other guy?
I'm Big Mom a.k.a Charlotte
Linlin's fourth son, Oven.
This looks like fun. I want in!
Seriously! I was curious about the fuss
and got lucky enough to hear the big reveal!
Sorry, Uta, but you're going
to be my gift to Mama!
Hang on.
It'll be okay.
Whoa, woah!
If any of you scumbags are after Uta-chan,
you'll have to go through me!
I can hardly ignore the kind of rogues who
would interrupt such a stirring performance.
Now this is my idea of entertainment!
Don't mess with the Jellyfish Pirates!
Song of Scratches... Blizzard Slice!
Kraken Fist!
I guess we're doing this!
The show's just getting started!
Let's get it on! We're gonna protect Uta!
Fishman Karate! Spear Wave!
I can super take it from here!
Gum-Gum... Jet Gatling!
Cien Fleurs! Spider Net!
Alrighty!
Okay! That's enough!
Luffy, guys, thanks for protecting me!
But no more brawling!
You think this is just a brawl?!
You're all my fans, so I want you all
enjoying the show and getting along!
But these guys are trying
to kidnap you, Princess Uta!
And they don't seem like the reasonable type!
When we want something, we fight to take it!
Because we're pirates!
So stop being pirates, then.
I'll forgive all the bad stuff
you've done until now.
Why don't all of you give up
this nasty pirate business
and join me in a world
with tons of fun instead?
With my songs, we can all
be happy and enjoy peace!
There's no such thing as peace, girl.
If you wanna keep yapping,
I can slice your face up!
Hang on! She belongs to me.
--Uta!
--It's fine.
Come on, I thought you all came
here to enjoy my singing.
We're pirates, baby. There's stuff that
matters to us more than music!
This is awful!
They're ruining the concert...
They don't care how Uta or any of us feel.
What a shame.
In that case, I'll make a song out of you.
Now, let worry fall away
No fear allowed to stay
My dream is now your wish
And my hope is never-ending
When clouds build up inside
My song can clear the sky
You know I'm invincible
Everything is alright
My voice carries birds in flight
With ev'ry note, they go higher and higher
See how I move with such grace
Just like a dancer on the stage
Your voice carries life within
Calls me to action again and again
If you're hurt and you need me
I'll always be there, I swear
I'll always protect you
We'll have the chance to go
to brand new heights
You and I, unstoppable when we're together
We can have it all
A fire burns within in our hearts
Now, let's go hand in hand
To a light that lies ahead
All of hopes and dreams
Can bring happiness when we're in sync
I've always felt this warmth from you
No one gives affection like you do
You make me invincible
When you're here by my side
Strong with you by my side
Okay, guys, those bad pirates
are now apart of a fun song!
Everything should be fine now, so you can relax!
That's right! They might be family,
but Uta is nothing like Shanks!
Thank goodness!
You're real strong now, Uta!
She's gotta have some kind of power, right?
Not that I'm aware of, but maybe...
What the heck is this?
What're you doing? Let's get back to our seats!
Now, I've got some great news
to share with you all!
I would always get tired during the streaming
concerts with Video Transponder Snails,
so they tended to be pretty short...
But this concert is an endless one!
It's gonna keep going, non-stop!
That's right! We can be together, forever!
Everybody watching the broadcast
and everyone here at the venue!
Let's all keep having a great time!
This is crazy! She's gonna do
a non-stop solo show?!
How cool is that?!
U-T-A! U-T-A! U-T-A!
U-T-A! U-T-A! U-T-A! U-T-A...!
And there's one other thing I need to say.
To all you pirates, the Navy,
and to the people at the World Government.
do not try to stop this concert.
Everyone is looking for fun
and things to make them happy.
If you ruin that... there'll be consequences.
I'm Uta, the woman who's
going to create a new age.
And I'm going to use my songs
to make everyone happy!
Okay, let's move to the next number.
Highest Authorities of the World Government
The Five Elders
Red-Haired had a Daughter all along, eh?
Cipher Pol's report was accurate.
This is a new threat, one that's
opposed to the Great Pirate Era.
The real problem is how she has popular support.
We should end any seeds of
rebellion before it's too late.
Even if this girl is of Figarland Blood?
I'm concerned about the presence
of Tot Musica as well.
Tot Musica...
With the threat it poses if awoken,
we can't afford to be cautious.
Yeah. The order to subdue Uta has just come in.
She's too damn dangerous.
It's funny enough that a single girl
has the whole world's attention.
Hey! You better not take her lightly!
The target's on the island of Music, Elegia.
The same spot where Tot Musica
was sealed away in ancient times.
And what kind of numbers are we sending?
How many ships are ready to set sail for Elegia?
Thirty.
Good! Send them all,
loaded for bear with troops!
--In the event of Transponder Snail interference,
orders from the flagship will be issued
--Code has been issued to crews already and orders
are to prepare response flags immediately.
--In the event of Transponder Snail interference,
orders from the flagship will be issued
--Code has been issued to crews already and orders
are to prepare response flags immediately.
--using the flag signals notated under
Code 044 in the Signal Book...
Okay, are any of you hungry?
In that case, I'm gonna make plenty
of food and other stuff to enjoy!
Can I really keep it?
Of course!
I want you all to eat whenever you want,
wherever you want!
Sing and dance with me and have a good time!
It's like a dream...
Stick with me and all your
dreams will come true!
There's nothing to scare us anywhere!
This new age is the greatest!
Her power's even greater than expected!
I suppose we've underestimated her.
And on top of that, she's Red-Haired's daughter?
I want her, no matter what it takes.
Those pain-in-the-neck Straw
hats are with her, too!
I'd like to see them try and take me on. Lick!
I'll go to Elegia.
I'm not going to stay quiet
when she's captured my sister.
This place is a real chef's paradise.
I asked Uta for booze and she whipped it up.
I know! I bet we could ask her
to create all kinds of treasure.
How do you think her powers work?
--Woah, there...
--She's a little too versatile
to have just eaten a Devil Fruit.
You've got a point.
I've never heard of powers
capable to be doing all this.
Luffy, you're friends with Uta, right?
Do you know anything?
She always really loved singing!
Huh?
Perhaps Uta has been gifted with
almighty powers from the gods of music!
Luffy. Guys. You having fun?
Yes, Princess Uta!
With all these unusual ingredients?
This place is heaven!
There's so much fun stuff!
I'm glad I could make Luffy's friends happy.
Hey, is this everyone?
Yep.
That can't be right. That hat belongs to--
This is everybody!
It's been a while, Luffy,
so how about another game?
There's no way you can beat me now.
What are you talking about?
I'm on a 183-game-long winning streak!
Wrong! I won those 183 times!
Those are extremely divergent perspectives.
What kind of game?
Luffy and I used to compete all the time.
At knife throwing, arm wrestling...
Okay! This is what we're gonna do today!
Whoa!
It's a game of chicken!
Whoever eats fastest wins.
Oh, I remember this! That just leaves...
Don't worry. I've got it covered!
Let's do this!
Ready...
Three, two, one, go!
For you.
Thanks!
Uta won!
She wins!
That was cheap, Uta!
Aw, crap, right into the ocean.
Oh, right! You ate a Devil Fruit, too,
huh, Luffy? Sorry about that!
You cheated back there! I want a do-over!
There you go again, being a sore loser!
And since I won, you better
tell me where Shanks is!
I dunno.
Then why've you got his straw hat?
He let me borrow it.
Hey, question!
Where did you two meet, anyway?
She came to Fusha Village
along with Shanks and his crew!
That's your hometown, isn't it?
Yeah!
12 years ago
Uta's daydreaming again!
You should come up here.
No way! Boring!
I wanna play a game instead!
Honestly, you're such a baby.
In that case, how about...
A game of chicken!
Winner eats the most then runs away.
Yeah!
That's dangerous! Cut that out, you two.
No way!
Uta! Luffy!
Let them have their fun.
This is their idea of serious competition.
Let's do it!
Ready...
Three, two, one, go!
What are they competing over, anyway?
Who's going to become
the bigger pirate, apparently.
Is Luffy gonna win?
Here's some juice.
Thanks!
Luffy!
I can't believe he fell for it again!
You okay?
It's not over!
That didn't settle nothing!
You're being a sore loser again!
Well, you cheated, so you lose!
I'm a pirate! There's no such thing as cheating!
You got careless in a duel
because you're a dumb baby!
It's not like Shanks says
you're a real pirate yet!
Shut up! I'm Shanks' daughter!
Unlike you, I've been sailing and going
on adventures for years now!
That's a huge difference!
--Is not!
--Is, too!
In that case, let's fight to
settle it--like real pirates!
Fine with me!
Give it a rest already.
No real pirate would use
their sword on a kid, Shanks!
Don't be silly, that was just tough love.
But swords are sharp, not tough!
Aw, did you say love?
Does that mean you love me, Shanks?
Shanks!
Uta, Luffy, both of you need
to stop clinging to me!
How come you call your dad "Shanks," anyway?
He might be my dad, but he's also
my captain, and I idolize him!
Isn't he cool?
I'm feeling so good about beating
Luffy again, I think I'll sing!
Shanks, I wanna go sailing, too!
You're too rowdy for my crew.
What about Uta?!
She waits on the ship during battle.
There's no way you could sit still.
That's right! I'm the Red-Haired
Pirates' musician, Uta!
The girl who's gonna use music to make
a new age where everyone will be free!
Pay attention, our musician's taking the stage.
Where did it come from
Where could this wind be taking us?
I look up to the sky hoping for answers
But there is no reply
Where will it end up,
The song that I've been a vessel for?
I look within knowing I'll find the answer
Even on my own
Let's row out to the open sea
far as we can go
To the unknown
I've got to keep--
Okay, I get to sing next!
All right, let's hear it!
Come to think of it,
you disappeared all of a sudden.
It was sudden? How come?
Let's see... If I can remember right...
I used to wait for Shanks
and his crew to come back.
But one time...
Welcome back!
What kinda adventures did you have this time?
Huh? What's wrong?
Fine, I'll just ask Uta!
Uta! Uta!
I'll listen to you brag about
your adventures again!
Where are you, Uta?!
Shanks? Where'd Uta go?
Did... something happen to her?
Don't worry, Luffy.
Uta left the crew to become
a singer. That's all.
So why'd you stop wanting to be a pirate, Uta?
You used to love the Red-Haired Pirates so much!
I wanted to be a singer more than a pirate.
I mean, I've already got fans all over
the world after only two years!
What about you, Luffy? What are you doing now?
Are you joking? I'm a pirate!
Right... You're a pirate, huh?
Yeah! And I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates.
Hey, Luffy... You should quit being a pirate.
Why don't you live here, with us, and have fun?
Your friends are all fans of mine, right?
It'd be way better to stay here.
Hey! Are you listening, Luffy?
It was great seeing you again, Uta!
I ate some meat, so I'm gonna head
back to the Sunny and sleep.
Looks like you're doing what
you want, and that's good!
See ya!
I'm not letting you go.
All of you, and Luffy,
are staying here forever...
Where you're going to have fun, with me.
What the hell are you talking about?
Uta, I love your singing,
but forever is a little--
Nami-san!
Everyone! I found more pirates!
What should I do?
U-T-A!
U-T-A! U-T-A! U-T-A! U-T-A!
Okay!
I'll take care of the pirates for you, then!
I don't care if you know Luffy,
you're having a little too much fun.
What are these guys?!
There are more and more of them!
Arabesque Brick Fist!
Ouchie Finger!
Luffy...
This is your fault for being a pirate.
If you're really my friend,
then give up on being a pirate.
What are you talking about?!
I'm not doing this. Don't feel like it.
There's no reason for us to fight.
You might not want a fight, but I do!
Seis Fleurs! Slap!
Quit messing around, Uta!
My mem'ries so good and awful
It seems they gave me a grudge
But I have left bitterness
and resentment behind me
And it is all thanks to him
Look, it's the clowns who think they know
How crushing loneliness can be
You know nothing 'til you come with me
And run wild!
Release your rage
Let the winds of wrath blow them away
Not gonna live in compliance-iance-iance
I'm not playin' the victim, no more
Time to go rage
Let's punish them all
For their love; I'm done trying to trust
Not gonna live in compliance-iance-iance
Gonna play with fire, backlit
By the flames
What the heck are you doing? Let me go!
I can't... let you become the Pirate King.
What do you all think of pirates?
Pirates burnt my city down!
Pirates killed my husband!
Give my mom back!
No more pirates! Throw them out!
Princess Uta! Luffy would never do that!
Uta, let my crew go--!
Stay away from Uta! Dammed pirate!
Those Devil Fruit powers aren't scary
when you're weakened from seawater!
Hey, stop it!
I can't stand this--
Don't.
It'll be okay. We need to get
ready for the the next phase.
Barrier Ball!
L-Lomeo...?
Luffy-senpai, there's something
real nasty about Uta-sama!
I don't think we can take her!
I haven't... lost... yet!
There you go, being a sore loser!
There were more pirates in hiding, huh?
What the--?! Where the heck are we?!
Oh, so you're a fan of Uta-sama, too, Trafalgar?
Wrong. I'm a chaperone.
For Bepo.
Sorry.
Thanks, Tra-guy!
I wouldn't be laughing, Straw Hat-ya.
If we can't figure out that woman's power--
I'll take care of it!
I'm on a 184-win streak against Uta!
Oh, there you are!
Found you!
--It's Uta!
--Luffy-senpai!
We're getting out of here for now!
The pirates are running away!
Let's all team up and hunt them down!
The SWORD Transponder Snail's not working.
This is bad. Uta might be serious
about going through with her plan.
So SWORD has their eye on Uta, too?
You're Cipher Pol, right?
What are you doing here?
Save the interjurisdictional quarrels for later!
Can you use your Door-Door ability?
You sure you don't know too much?
No more than you.
I can, but out here, it'd be too big
of a drain on my stamina.
I see...
What's the call? We're running out of time.
We'll recruit more fighters.
For now, that's all we can do.
This sucks! They all got caught!
They're just stuck on those lines,
so it's probably fine, but...
I can't believe I get to
give Luffy-senpai a lift!
I'm so overwhelmed, I can't see in front of me!
Straw Hat!
Thanks.
What are you doing? We need to move!
There're so many of them!
They're gonna surround us for sure!
You boys...
You really saved us!
Your name is Luffy, then?
Yep!
--Then, you're...
--Who're you, old guy?
I am the former ruler of this nation,
Elegia. My name is Gordon.
What nation? This place has got all kinds
of buildings, but there's not a soul around!
No.
Elegia used to be known as the capital
of music for the entire world.
Before everyone who lived
there went missing overnight.
You mean to say a whole country
was gone in one night?
A certain big-name pirate
is rumored to be responsible.
Let me tell you about Uta.
Once Elegia's citizens were gone,
I raised Uta here, alone.
You did?
But it was only the two of us, by ourselves...
I'm sure she was lonely.
She put a brave face on around me,
but whenever she was alone,
she would sing about her lost friends...
I recall that day
we played together by the sea
Just you and me
Still that scent of ocean seems
to fade each passing day
It slips away
So I sing an old familiar song
I hope you know the one
I will sing to call you back to me
--I raised her to be the greatest
singer in the world
--I need you to hear it
Need you to believe in
--in an effort to put more joy into her voice.
--I need you to hear it
Need you to believe in
--in an effort to put more joy into her voice.
--Something out there...
Excuse me?! Are you listening?!
Just keep talking, old timer.
Sorry.
Anyway, I guess that explains how Uta-sama
doesn't know what Luffy-senpai's been up to.
Sorry!
The greatest question I faced
was when and how
to present her sublime singing to the world.
She grew up almost entirely
ignorant of outside affairs...
But then, the time came in a way
I couldn't have anticipated.
It was two years ago...
She stumbled upon something...
A new type of Video Transponder Snail
had washed up on the beach.
Uta started sending her songs beyond the island,
like she had been set free from something.
Her voice charmed many fans,
and spread quickly enough to fill
every corner of the globe.
Thanks, Uta!
I feel better now!
I think I'll make it through another
day tomorrow thanks to you!
Me, too. I'm so glad you all like my singing!
But as she learned about
the state of the outside world,
she started to develop
awareness to something else...
Of how the Great Pirate Era was one
of unending war and bloodshed.
It started with just her singing,
but in time, fans were starting
to hail Uta as some kind of savior.
And Uta, in response...
I understand how all of you feel.
And if that's what you need,
then I'll create a new age for you!
Please! You have to stop Uta's plan!
You were her friend, Luffy!
You should be able to do it!
Does this plan of hers involve the concert--?
Sorry!
Bepo!
--Bepo?!
--The bear!
Uta...
Gordon. What are you doing with these pirates?
Uta, how come you left Shanks' ship?
You said you were the
Red-Haired Pirates' musician.
You could always go back to him!
Shut up...
I don't want to talk about Shanks anymore!
Seriously, Luffy,
Give up the One Piece,
being a pirate king, and Shanks' hat...
Forget all that dumb stuff
and just enjoy life with me!
Hey! That's going too far!
We could eat all kinds of tasty food,
and play chicken, or arm wrestle!
Just laughing and living our lives,
like we used to.
Give the hat back! That's Shanks' hat!
Fine, Luffy. I don't need you in my new age.
Room! Shambles!
Huh? Where'd they go?
Did the pirates get away?
Huh... I guess there are
all kinds of different powers.
Oh, well! Let's make it a game!
Try to find the runaway pirates!
Let me out! I gotta get my hat back!
Shut up! You're staying in there
because you can't pull that off!
But we can't just keep running...
We'll head to the opposite end
of the island, then to the port.
The port?
There were Marines and intelligence
agents in the audience.
What're they doing here?
It means the World Government and Navy
have already noticed Uta's power
and consider her to be a threat.
They were keeping an eye on her?
If we can find someone near the island
from the Navy and get them to talk,
we might learn how her power--
Wrong way!
Not a problem! My barriers are real strong!
But it keeps rolling!
We're real high!
Luffy-senpai! I'm begging you,
you gotta hold it in!
Hey, Gordon... are you mad?
About me doing this concert without asking you?
It's not just a concert, is it?
You noticed? You'll support me, right?
I... I've...
Must be nice to be able to have
that choice. To chicken out.
I don't want you doing this!
But--
Just wait there for now.
The World Government
and Navy will come after you!
It's fine. Because I have this.
No... Tot Musica!
I knew about how you hid it beneath the castle.
Why didn't you throw it away?
Maybe you were hoping for
the dawn of a new age, too.
Uta! You can't use that! It's--
Uta!
The sea's real big. Real vast.
But I don't see anybody, much less the Navy.
She's gone!
Who is?
The Sunny's missing!
Your ship?!
Sunny!
Sunny... Sunny... Sunny.
No way!
Is that you, Sunny?!
Did Uta-sama's power do this, too?!
I'm seriously freaking out!
Sunny?
Reports are coming in from the forecastle decks:
No sign of the enemy in the vicinity.
--Repeat, no sign of enemies in the vicinity.
--Make sure we haven't been followed.
Armed scouting team one has landed and is moving
through the ruins. No signs of the enemy.
Armed scouting team two is continuing
the search, but no trace of the enemy so far.
Mission is underway, but unable
to confirm enemy presence.
Awaiting further orders.
What in the world happened?
This is armed scouting team seven.
No intel found on Elegian citizens.
Armed scout team two, unable to
find any hostiles in the vicinity.
This is armed scout team four with
a message for Vice Admiral Mononaga.
The audience is still unconscious,
I repeat, still unconscious.
They're not dead, are they?
Just sleeping!
But they're not waking up, no matter what.
And if you kill me, nobody here
is going to get their soul back...
You think that's a good idea?
Miss.
I believe I understand pretty well
how your Devil Fruit power works.
Great, that saves me an explanation!
Go ahead and leave, then.
Besides, it won't be long
until I'm gone, anyway.
This scent... Is that a Wake-shroom?
Wake-shroom?
Those who eat them are unable to sleep,
and in time, they die.
Woman! Do you want to take the entire
audience with you when you die?!
What does death matter?
Isn't the soul more important than the body?
In the new age, everyone is going
to be living together, in soul!
I'd rather not shed any blood today.
Is there any way you'll reconsider this plot
of yours to turn the world on its head?
Huh? What even is that?
I just want everyone to be happy!
I can tell you're not one to listen to reason.
And neither are you guys.
Not so fast!
With your singing voice blocked out,
your powers are nothing!
Nice try. But you're too late.
Captain Koby? What in the
world's gotten into you?
Everyone! The bad guys are here!
Let's beat them up together
for our new era!
Don't hurt them! These are
innocent civilians she's controlling!
I'm sick and tired of being alone
Wanna be connected
Have a bond to hold on to
Just gonna lay it all out, how I feel
Honest (Shout out!)
Listen baby makin' you happy
Whether you like it or not
Gonna be up in your ears
No run-in away just wait for the beat to drop
Listen for a surprise
Every word will entice
You think you're so tough?
Well I've had enough of it
I got something here that's better
Come on up and we can sing together
Fun unfettered
Get on stage, let's go
(Ha-how!) Wanna make your day
Do my thing loud and proud (Hey!)
No shame in what I create
I got this down
Everything exactly how we want it
This is a utopia
Been a long time comin', now it's here to stay
You can't deny
It's a miracle of mercy
You can't stop it if you try
I know it's possible
I'm not tryin' ask too much
Salvation's got to come
This generation's done
It's tired of never being listened to
The screams were never heard
The suffering endured
But no more!
Watch me rock this
They got nothin'
Up to me,
You just need to stay out of my way
There's no turnin' back now
Gonna be singin' jointly for all time
Blowin' your mind with my pace
Drummin' to burst your ear drum
Bring in the bass, guitar and keys
Macaferri got nothin' on me, no
Ooo-wah! Oh let me hear you shout!
Ooo-wah Ow-oo-wow
Banish every gaslight
Let clarity shine
Gotta clean up this brainwash
Don't let 'em tell you lies
Heads up, let my song clear your senses
All you really need
Is my true voice
Dammit, it's no good! We're stuck.
That was one pathetic display.
You're just as stuck as I am, Moss Head!
Franky, Jimbei, any luck?
It won't budge at all!
Likewise.
Brook?
I can almost...
Are you almost free?
I can almost see... Nami-san's panties.
Say what?!
You look, you die!
Can I say something?
Uta said she'd make us into a song, didn't she?
Maybe we're arranged on a staff for a reason.
It does appear to be some kind of melody...
Maybe our heads are where the notes are?
Can you sing it, Brook?
I can't see the entire score...
Right now I can most easily see...
--some underwear.
--Shut up! And don't look!
You noticed you were arranged on a score...
The Straw Hat crew never fails to impress.
Huh?
What are you two doing with Blueno?
Explanations can wait for now.
Here, sing this.
Mi! Re!
Finally free!
Come on, keep it going, Brook!
It seems you've got a grasp of the girl's power.
Hey!
Could you at least set my sister free?
Big Brother...
You cooperate with the Navy.
Even if it's temporary.
Mi...
Mi!
Do re...
Thank you. You are a magnificent little bear.
Aye-aye!
Why... are we still in here?!
I can't let you loose until we know
for sure what Uta-sama's power are!
Sunny!
Sun... Sunny?
Who're you?!
It's good to see you again, Luffy-san.
Koby! Get me... out of here!
How'd you find us?
I was able to sense Luffy-san's presence.
Observation Haki, huh?
After that, Blueno-san let us
use his Door-Door ability.
Let me out with your Door-Door...
Care to explain why Cipher Pol
and the Navy are working together?
It's Uta's powers you really
want to know about, right?
You know how they work?!
This will be hard to believe,
but this world... It isn't reality.
Everything you're seeing...
...it's an imaginary world created in our
minds by Uta's Sing-Sing Fruit ability.
The power of the Sing-Sing Fruit is to draw people's
soul into this world after hearing the user sing.
Those who are affected
feel like they're in a world
where Uta makes the rules
instead of reality.
It's like everyone is dreaming the same dream.
Come to think of it, Uta mentioned
having a power like that.
So that's why everybody would fall
asleep when listening to her sing!
Would've been a big help
if you'd said something sooner!
I forgot!
So... what's going on in reality?
Our bodies are still there,
but Uta has control over them.
How do we get back to the real world?
If Uta sleeps, her power will cease to function.
But while we're in the world of the
Sing-Sing Fruit, we can't affect her in reality.
If she's using a Devil Fruit power,
it has to have a limit.
You're right.
Maintaining the Sing-Sing world
is an incredible drain on her stamina.
Sort of like how I can't constantly
use the Door-Door Fruit's power.
So we'll be okay once Uta-sama
gets tired enough to fall asleep?
That's not likely.
Before the concert started, she was confirmed
to be eating Wake-shrooms.
They keep people who eat them from sleeping.
It won't be long before Uta, in the real world,
runs out of strength... and dies.
She's gonna die?
Uta?
Will we be released, then?
No, the opposite.
When Uta dies, this world
will be cut off from reality.
And everyone in it...
us included, will be stuck here.
Trapping all her fans in the Sing-Sing World...
That's what Uta has been planning.
That's totally nuts!
Koby, how do we stop Uta?
That's what I came here to
find out, but I'm still not sure.
But the more fighting strength
we have, the better,
so Helmeppo is gathering the pirates
who've been trapped here.
The Straw Hat crew also appears
to be taking some action.
Then they're okay!
They were headed for the Elegia castle.
Nico Robin seems to know something about
what happened on this island ages ago.
If there're any records on what happened,
it might help us learn how
to get around Uta's power.
Not a lot to pin our hopes to...
Have a little faith in Robin-chan,
you stupid Moss Head!
It's just the facts, Twirly Brow!
They said there's a room with
a bunch of books over there!
Everyone, let's forget about those pirates
and wait for the dawn of the new era!
How long until Uta dies in reality?
Should be less than two hours left.
With walls this soundproof, I doubt
Uta's powers can reach us here.
The Navy boys mentioned that anywhere
beyond the sound of her voice would be safe.
Are these all history books?
How are we supposed to get through all of this?!
Three-Sword Style! Ultra Tiger Hunt!
Diable Jambe... Frites Assorties!
Strong Right! Weapons Left!
Robin, look through the books!
--But--
--Robin!
We'll keep them off you, don't worry!
It won't be long before we're in
a new age... with no bad people.
Do you read me?
Uta has an hour left, at most.
But the Video Transponder Snails,
with their souls stolen, are out of control...
They're continuing to broadcast footage
from the Sing-Sing World.
They need to be muted to avoid trouble.
The second someone hears her singing,
their soul will be captured.
Listen baby makin' you happy
Whether you like it or not
Gonna be up in your ears
No run-in' away just wait for the beat to drop
Listen for a surprise
Every word will entice
You think you're so tough?
Well, I've had enough of it
I got something here that's better
Come on up and we can sing together
Fun unfettered
Get on stage, let's go (Ha-how!)
It's been six hours since Uta began her concert.
The number of victims has been
increasing at an exponential rate.
If things proceed at this rate, in one hour,
the estimate is that 70% of the world's
population will be pulled into the Sing-Sing World.
Seventy percent?
That's worse than we anticipated.
This could mean the end of the world.
She needs to be stopped somehow.
Nice!
Very nice-eh!
You're coming home with me
to sing me a lullaby-eh!
A Celestial Dragon...
Saint Charloss is requesting your presence.
You should be grateful.
I'll pay a billion for you-eh!
Wait, are you one of those Celestial Dragons?
I know about them! It was in a book.
They rule the world and want
to make slaves out of everyone.
They're the most hated people in the world!
You need to cut it out before you upset him.
You guys are Marines?
You must've taken leave to
come and see me! Thanks!
Never mind that. You will obey Saint Charloss
and accompany us to the Holy Land.
No way.
Everyone's equal here!
And we're glad to have this
old Celestial Dragon join us!
Old?! She gets an execution-eh!
Seriously, there's no point.
If you're useless, I don't need you-eh.
How could you do that?!
It's okay. I'll save you.
What are you Marines doing-eh?!
Kill this little wench-eh!
I thought the Navy was supposed
to represent justice...
The Celestial Dragons might as well be gods...
I get it! You don't really want to follow
this jerk's orders, do you?
In that case, don't worry about it!
In the new era, Celestial Dragons
and slaves will all be equal!
Equality?! How revolting!
All of you, hurry and kill her-eh!
It's not personal, girl...
Huh?
Don't... think... you'll get...
away with tharrgble!
You guys don't have to be afraid
of the Celestial Dragons anymore!
This... This isn't a good idea, Uta!
If you mess with a Celestial Dragon...
...the World Government and Navy
will hunt you down!
I'm telling you, it's fine!
Sorry, Uta!
I should be heading home by now.
I've got sheep to look after.
Thanks! I had a great time!
Hang on... I don't understand...
Why would you want to go back
to a life that's so hard and painful
when you could enjoy life here instead?
Most importantly, anyone know what happened
to the pirates I had captured before?
Uta-san, this needs to stop now!
You're a Marine, too?
You here to save the Celestial Dragon?
I'm here to save lives!
You need to release everyone's souls
so they can return to reality.
Captain Koby?!
Is he famous or something?
He's the hero who saved people
during the Rocky Port incident!
Really? I've been on Elegia all this time,
so I haven't kept up with the news.
W-Well...
Hey, hero.
I've used my power too much.
You have to tell them.
Right.
Everyone, please listen!
The truth is, this world that
we're in is not reality.
You've all been lied to!
We should leave this place as soon as possible!
Uta... did you really...
lie to us and trap us here?!
It's not a lie!
I haven't lied to anybody!
You've got it all wrong, guys!
I'm just trying to lead you to happiness!
This is the place you've all dreamed of.
The Great Pirate Era is over!
It's going to be an age of freedom
and peace instead!
Isn't that fantastic?!
There'll be plenty of food and games!
There'll be no mean people,
no sickness, no pain!
Yeah... I guess it would be happier living here.
Me, too!
Right?! I knew it!
But... I've got work...
I'm trying to tell you, you don't
have to work! Or study...
But still... I don't want to stay here forever.
There're things I've put a lot of work into.
And the idea of playing around all the time...
I wanna go home.
This would completely
change civilization, right?
I don't think I can go along with this...
Even if it is Uta's idea...
Uta-san, you should cancel your--
Hang on a second!
Everyone! I thought you wanted to be free!
Were you lying when you said you wanted
no more diseases or bullying?!
You told me you didn't want to spend
every day afraid of pirates!
I'm telling you, I want to go home, dammit!
Stop that! Uta has done
all of this for our sake!
I never asked her to!
Same here!
You guys need to shut up!
I agree with Uta!
I don't like this.
I liked going to school!
What difference does tha t make?
A big one!
Uta's goin g too far!
You're awful!
What did you just say to me?!
Okay! Sorry, I get it now!
You just need to have more fun, right?!
See? You're all having fun now, right?!
Everyone! Let's all enjoy a free and
peaceful new age together, forever!
Saint Charloss!
We can't afford more casualties.
The time has come to make a decision.
Even if a Celestial Dragon
is caught in the crossfire...
Well, we barely made it out of there.
Who the heck are you?!
Blueno.
Koby, did you see Uta?
Well...
I'm guessing negotiations have fallen through.
How about you guys?
Check it out!
Hold on! I didn't hear anything
about working with Straw Hat!
I'd rather die!
See ya!
Wait a minute--
We'll figure out our own way of beating Uta!
Sunny...
What about my crew?
Still not back.
If they can't find Uta's weakness,
we're out of options.
And I can't use my Door-Door
ability in this body...
It'll be fine. Knowing my gang...
Rolling... Exploding Star!
How's that?!
"The fears and doubts of men...
given the name Tot Musica.
Now flee and cower."
Kung Fu Point!
Mirage Tempo!
Diable Jambe!
Collier Strike!
One-Sword Style... Demon Horse!
Soul Parade... Ice Burn!
Fishman Karate! Sharkskin Palm Thrust!
Radical Beam! Giant Slalom!
Uh-oh! It's gonna collapse!
What idiot started blowing stuff up indoors?!
Super sorry about that!
We'll be buried alive!
Come to think of it, I'd look right at home!
This way, Robin!
Brulee! I know you're in there!
Let us into Mirro-world right now!
Quit ignoring me!
You realize without our intel, you'll be stuck
in the Sing-Sing World, too, right?!
You'll never see your precious
friends and family again.
You okay with that?!
Not even Big Bro Katakuri...?
N-No!
You guys! You made it!
Luffy!
Sunny!
Who's that supposed to be?
It's Sunny!
She's so cute!
What kind of mods did that?!
Can't believe we ended up back here...
Sorry, Big Bro Oven.
Robin-san, did you discover how to beat Uta?
The old records say that those
trapped in the Sing-Sing World
won't be able to return to reality
under their own power. No matter what.
But if someone with the Sing-Sing Fruit powers
uses Tot Musica, there'll be a chance.
Tot Musica?
An entity from ancient times
created from human emotions.
Loneliness, sadness...
the shadows that fall on the soul.
It's been called a Demon King before as well.
Is it some kind of weapon?
The part I was able to read
only mentioned avoiding it.
So if the Sing-Sing Fruit user breaks this
taboo, what kind of chance will we get?
The records say that when the Demon King
is summoned with Tot Musica,
it'll appear both in the world created by
the Sing-Sing Fruit as well as in reality.
The Demon King acts as a link between
the two worlds at that point.
And if the Demon King is attacked
in both worlds at the same time...
...he'll be defeated, and that
will erase the song world.
Really?!
I doubt there'd be a record
unless it worked before.
We've gotta try it!
Who's gonna attack Uta-sama in reality, though?
Well, we're all stuck in here...
The only people who could strike in
reality would be the Navy or Cipher--
No.
They won't make a move
with civilian lives at stake.
As valuable as this intel is,
without someone to work within reality...
There is someone.
Captain!
Is that Bepo? Seriously?
And who's the old guy?
That's Uta-sama's adoptive father, Gordon-san!
Uta-chan's dad?
So who exactly are you talking about?
Shanks...
Shanks?!
When Shanks arrives,
he'll be able to stop Uta in reality.
Old guy, did something happen
between Uta and Shanks?
Well...
Old guy!
Ah! He's going straight to Uta-sama!
And we can't beat her yet!
There's no stopping our captain
when he gets like that.
We're running out of time anyway.
Might as well join him and put an end to this.
But how?
If we need simultaneous attacks,
we'll start hitting her and won't stop...
...until the attack on the other side starts
and the timing matches up.
I feel like a punk for chickening out!
There's no way we can lose
with the Straw Hats backing us!
We've got no other choice.
Yeah!
So... I was wondering...
What happened to you?
Now you ask?
What are you doing here?
You can fight me over and over,
but you'll never win.
It's not over yet.
There you go again, you sore loser!
Then, I guess we'll settle this with
a fight, like we used to, Luffy.
You're not even trying to hit me.
What you're doing is wrong!
I could say that to you, Luffy.
You need to realize that
the Great Pirate Era is over.
Why do you wanna be the King
of the Pirates so bad, anyway?
To make a new era.
Luffy--!
The Great Pirate Era began
with Roger's execution...
Now, Luffy, it's gonna end with yours!
Don't do it!
Uta!
You... You used to love the
Red-Haired Pirates so much!
You used to love Shanks so much!
Why do you hate pirates now?!
It's Shanks' fault.
I thought of him...
...like my own father!
I considered everyone on that ship to be family!
But that was just a lie they told me!
That's why... Shanks abandonded me!
He left me behind on Elegia!
He said it was so you could be a singer!
Wrong!
Magnificent! Your voice is a gift to the world!
There's no shortage of experts,
instruments, and music here.
We would love for you to join us in Elegia!
The entire country would welcome you!
You seemed to really enjoy singing back there.
Hm? I guess...
You sure you wouldn't rather sing
for a big crowd instead of for us?
It's not like that.
Y'know, Uta...
Things like peace and equality
don't really exist in the world.
But your voice...
It's the one thing that can bring happiness
to everyone in the world.
What are you talking about?
You can stay, if you want.
I'll come pick you up once you're
the greatest singer in the world.
Stupid! I'm the Red-Haired Pirates' musician!
If you're asking me to choose between learning
about music and leaving... leaving you guys...
Okay, I get it!
You've got a point. We can ship out tomorrow.
But that night...
Gordon-san?
You're awake?
What happened?
Where are Shanks and the others?!
They took everything!
Everyone... they're all dead...
Where is Shanks?!
They used your singing voice to approach Elegia,
plotting to make off with our treasures...
You mean...?
The Red-Haired Pirates...
They've been lying to you this whole time!
The Red-Haired Pirates! And Shanks!
Shanks! Don't leave me!
Why...? Why would you do this?!
The country of music, Elegia, destroyed
Love and peace are trampled with only two survivors!
The Culprit is Red-Haired Shanks
Shanks would never do something like that!
And you know that!
Then explain the last 12 years!
You're nothing but a tool
for Shanks, too, Luffy!
Shanks is coming.
To save you?
To save you.
Me? Why?
You think he's gonna sit back while his
daughter pulls something like this?!
He abandoned me...
He's not coming.
Enough is enough, Luffy.
Bye-bye.
Shanks...?
Why?
It's been a while...
And I felt like hearing you sing.
This is perfect!
Soon, all my fans and I are
going to bring a new age.
And I wanted to settle up
with you before I did!
Everyone! The worst pirate of all is here!
Let's beat him together!
Shanks is here, isn't he?
Now!
You still want to fight? In that case...
--We can choose the way of our future
--Hold it right there!
--Sunny! Sunny--!
--Try a brand new path
Guard Point!
Room! Shambles!
Barrier Ball! Sound!
Uta-sama, that voice of yours
is trapped in here now!
Whoa, there.
Stow it, Gab!
You die before you fight back!
No! No!
Just hang on! The new age is almost here!
That's right. Deploy every last asset
the Navy has to eliminate Uta.
Doesn't matter if the audience go with her!
We're doing this to protect the world
before she threatens anyone else!
Annihilate her!
So, the self-righteous Navy is willing
to kill a bunch of civilians?
Is that it, Kizaru?!
No such thing as justice without sacrifices.
Ain't it a shame, having to sacrifice
thousands to kill one kid?
Yasakani Sacred Jewel!
Sorry, but this is kind of a family quarrel.
Mind keeping out of it?
I'm afraid that's not an option.
Not with the world on the line.
I'm asking you to back off anyway.
If I could do that sort of thing...
I'd still have my sight.
Hongo-san...
It looks like something's happening in reality.
She's definitely been eating Wake-shrooms.
They don't just keep people from sleeping,
they make you turn aggressive
and lose control of your emotions.
Bad guys need to look like bad guys.
I should've done this sooner.
Uta!
I wasn't brave enough...
I didn't have the courage to use it!
But I'm done being afraid!
Be careful. I'm pretty sure that's--
--ᚷᚨᚺ ᛉᚨᚾ ᛏᚨᚲ ᚷᚨᚺ ᛉᚨᚾ ᛏᚨᛏ ᛏᚨᛏ ᛒᚱᚨᚲ
--My perfect barrier...!
--That's...
--ᚷᚨᚺ ᛉᚨᚾ ᛏᚨᚲ ᚷᚨᚺ ᛉᚨᚾ ᛏᚨᛏ ᛏᚨᛏ ᛒᚱᚨᚲ
--Well, this is bad.
--We went to the trouble of preparing these,
--Wand'ring heart
Clouds above
--but now there's no point.
--Wand'ring heart
Clouds above
Rain begins to fall down
--My bitter tears flowing out
They never dry up
--This can't get much worse!
She's awoken it!
--My bitter tears flowing out
They never dry up
--This can't get much worse!
She's awoken it!
--I let the words of a curse
Be my deliverance
--The ancient Demon King, given form
--I let the words of a curse
Be my deliverance
--by the song of a Sing-Sing Fruit user...
--I let the words of a curse
Be my deliverance
--by the song of a Sing-Sing Fruit user...
--ᛗᛁᛖ ᚾᛖᚷ ᛟᚾ ᚷᛁᛖᚲ ᚷᛁᛖᚲ
ᚾᚨᚺ ᛈᚺᚨᛋ ᛏᛖᛉᛉᛖ ᛚᚨᚺ
--...Tot Musica!
--ᛗᛁᛖ ᚾᛖᚷ ᛟᚾ ᚷᛁᛖᚲ ᚷᛁᛖᚲ
ᚾᚨᚺ ᛈᚺᚨᛋ ᛏᛖᛉᛉᛖ ᛚᚨᚺ
These ancient words
like a hymn of reclamation
Not even death will escape them
How to center these
troubled thoughts? I pray
Can the future bring calm
to the sea? I beg
Keep making this music
'til you breathe your last
We dream but never lose sight of the past
Illuminate hope and forget all the rest
Nothing left but to yell, yeah, yeah
It's time for salvation to finally come
I feel this rage, and I'm feelin' it strong
This weeping and wailing
has gone far too long
Nothing left but to yell! Yeah! Yeah!
I know you feel it, too
So keep on singin' this song
Even when they abuse us
We'll keep singing along
We'll start another Big Bang
When we all sing as one
United, we're fightin'--
--There's no cutting the sound.
--ᚷᚨᚺ ᛉᚨᚾ ᛏᚨᚲ ᚷᚨᚺ ᛉᚨᚾ ᛏᚨᛏ ᛏᚨᛏ ᛒᚱᚨᚲ
--It doesn't matter! There's no point.
--Reality and the song world have been linked
--ᚷᚨᚺ ᛉᚨᚾ ᛏᚨᚲ ᚷᚨᚺ ᛉᚨᚾ ᛏᚨᛏ ᛏᚨᛏ ᛒᚱᚨᚲ
--by the Demon King...
--Wand'ring heart
Clouds above
Rain begins to fall down
--My bitter tears flowing out
They never dry up
--Uta! Uta, please, stop!
--My bitter tears flowing out
They never dry up
--Uta, can you hear us?!
--My bitter tears flowing out
They never dry up
--Uta, can you hear us?!
--I let the words of a curse
Be my deliverance
--This world... it's not what you talked about!
--I let the words of a curse
Be my deliverance
--Uta!
--ᛗᛁᛖ ᚾᛖᚷ ᛟᚾ ᚷᛁᛖᚲ ᚷᛁᛖᚲ
ᚾᚨᚺ ᛈᚺᚨᛋ ᛏᛖᛉᛉᛖ ᛚᚨᚺ
ᛗᛁᛖ ᚾᛖᚷ ᛟᚾ ᚷᛁᛖᚲ ᚷᛁᛖᚲ
These ancient words
like a hymn of reclamation
Not even death will escape them
--How to center these
troubled thoughts? I pray
--Uta!
--How to center these
troubled thoughts? I pray
--Uta!
--Can the future bring calm
to the sea? I beg
Can the future bring calm
Keep making this music
'til you breathe your last
We dream but never lose sight of the past
Illuminate hope and forget all the rest
Nothing left but to yell, yeah, yeah
It's time for salvation to finally come
I feel this rage, and I'm feelin' it strong
This weeping and wailing
has gone far too long
--Nothing left but yell! Yeah! Yeah!
--Heat Beating!
--I know you feel it, too
So keep on singin' this song
I know you feel it, too
Even when they abuse us
We'll keep singing along
We'll start another Big Bang
When we all sing as one
United, we're fightin',
bring 'em down with our song of ruin
--Dammit! This won't work
if we can't hit her simultaneously!
--ᚷᚨᚺ ᛉᚨᚾ ᛏᚨᚲ ᚷᚨᚺ ᛉᚨᚾ ᛏᚨᛏ ᛏᚨᛏ ᛒᚱᚨᚲ
--Princess Uta!
--How could you use a voice that
was supposed to save people for this?!
--ᚷᚨᚺ ᛉᚨᚾ ᛏᚨᚲ ᚷᚨᚺ ᛉᚨᚾ ᛏᚨᛏ ᛏᚨᛏ ᛒᚱᚨᚲ
--Usopp!
--I'm fine...
--ᚷᚨᚺ ᛉᚨᚾ ᛏᚨᚲ ᚷᚨᚺ ᛉᚨᚾ ᛏᚨᛏ ᛏᚨᛏ ᛒᚱᚨᚲ
--Leave Tot Musica to us!
--So, please...!
--ᚷᚨᚺ ᛉᚨᚾ ᛏᚨᚲ ᚷᚨᚺ ᛉᚨᚾ ᛏᚨᛏ ᛏᚨᛏ ᛒᚱᚨᚲ
--Don't leave Uta-chan alone up there.
--Go and finish it!
--ᚷᚨᚺ ᛉᚨᚾ ᛏᚨᚲ ᚷᚨᚺ ᛉᚨᚾ ᛏᚨᛏ ᛏᚨᛏ ᛒᚱᚨᚲ
Hey! I bet you can hear me now, Uta!
This is all--
Luffy-senpai!
Luffy!
What are you doing?! Fight back!
Uta! Listen to me!
Uta... we need to talk...
I have nothing to say... to a pirate!
Old guy!
Bepo?!
I cannot let Uta hurt any more of her friends...
But this dummy still believes in Shanks.
You're wrong, Uta. I lied...
Twelve years ago... on that night, it wasn't the
Red-Haired Pirates who destroyed Elegia...
It was Tot Musica!
I'm sorry... that I never
told you the truth before.
Do you remember the party from that day?
When the musicians of the city learned,
you were leaving with Shanks,
they realized it was their last-chance
and had you sing non-stop.
and arranged it so that your singing
would play throughout the land.
And that was a mistake.
That singing beckoned to a score that
had been sealed deep under the castle!
That score... was Tot Musica...
It found its way to your side and tempted you
so that it would be set free
with your Sing-Sing Fruit powers!
With the seal on the Demon King
broken, he absorbed you,
and unleashed his wrath on the country!
Snap out of it, Uta!
Don't let him take you!
Your youth ended up saving us.
You were exhausted and fell asleep.
But... the country was...
The Navy is already here.
Would you mind keeping this a secret from Uta?
It'd be cruel to tell her the truth.
Right. I'll tell the Navy
that I was responsible.
Nah. It should be us.
"Red-Haired" Shanks and his crew,
the Red-Haired Pirates, did this.
Tell that to Uta, too.
You're going to leave her...?
The girl's got a hell of a voice.
We can't keep her cooped up on a boat
while we're on the run from the Navy.
Please. Make her into the
greatest singer in the world.
Her singing isn't a crime.
Shanks...
I understand!
As the king of Elegia, I, Gordon, swear upon
the love my subjects felt for music!
I will turn Uta into a sublime singer,
who will spread joy to the entire world!
Uta... even when we're apart,
you'll always be my daughter, so...
Let's part with a smile!
Our beloved musician is setting off on her own!
Uta! You heard him!
I knew Shanks was a good guy!
That's... my old drawing!
It's done! Boom!
What is it?
It's Shanks' straw hat!
A hat?
Yeah!
You suck.
Let's make it the mark of our new age!
You take that. Don't lose it!
Stop, Uta.
This isn't freedom.
This isn't a new age!
You know that better than anyone!
Luffy--
--Luffy!
--We're too late...
What is this?
Get in here if you want to be safe!
Hey! How the hell are we
supposed to fight that thing?!
If we just knew how to time
the simultaneous attacks...!
Well, isn't that funny?
The Navy's ready to kill civilians
and the pirates are protecting them.
I don't think titles matter right now.
Why protect them all?
Because our daughter doesn't need
anything else on her conscience!
All, right, you bozos!
Nobody else dies today!
Stopping the Demon King might be faster...
Uta's been eating Wake-shrooms.
If she's been consumed by Tot Musica,
I'm not sure how she can be stopped...
--Uta...
--You did it!
--It was your fault.
--You did this!
--You're guilty...
Shut up! I knew the truth!
It happened a year after I started
singing for everyone...
I found a Transponder Snail that recorded
what had happened on that day.
If you're watching this, look out!
The girl named Uta is dangerous!
Her song can destroy the world!
But what was I supposed to do at that point?!
The whole world is waiting
for my singing already!
Please, Uta. I don't want to be here anymore.
Isn't there a world where I can just listen
to your singing all the time?
That's right! I'm Uta and I hate pirates!
For all the people who found me...
I can't turn back anymore!
For the new age--!
Heat Goat!
Big Brother Oven!
Look out!
Can't let a lady get hurt, can I?
Besides, there's something
only you can do...
Right!
Koby, take command!
Right! Defensive formation!
Our main priority is protecting the audience!
Nami-san, Robin-san
please help organize the evacuation!
Ladies and gentlemen,
proceed calmly into the mirror!
Brulee-san is at the center of this operation!
Blueno-san, take your team and protect her!
Franky-san, Jimbei-san, guard our flanks!
Chopper-san, keep Luffy-san
and Gordon-san safe!
Helmeppo-san and I will join flank guard!
Usopp-san, provide fire support from the rear!
Brook-san, Sanji-san,
you'll be frontline defense!
Zoro-san will take point on attack,
along with Oven-san and Law-san!
Let's get to work.
Franky Rocket Launcher!
Yummy, yummy, yummy!
Yummy!
Zeus! Breeze Tempo!
Room!
Uta! This is my fault!
I was afraid of your power and missed
the chance to introduce you to the world!
And... And as a music lover,
I couldn't bring myself to throw
away the Tot Musica sheet!
I'm a damned fool! A coward who
keeps making excuses to run away!
I should be the only one who has to pay...
Y'know, my old man always left me on my own!
But you've been by Princess Uta's
side this whole time, right?
Keeping your promise,
even after your country was wiped out.
You're a heck of a guy!
Okay, I'm going.
Luffy?
Luffy-kun! Her singing... it has the power
to bring joy to the entire world!
For this to happen... it's just too tragic!
Please, Luffy-kun! Save Uta!
Of course I will.
Luffy-san!
Let him go! We're running out of time!
If we can't do this, we're not
making it back to reality!
Red-Haired!
You need to attack simultaneously.
At the same time and same point
as the attack in the Sing-Sing World.
What's Big Mom's son doing here?
I'm here to save my sister!
Observation Haki lets me see the other side
through my sister's eyes for an instant.
This thing is acting as a bridge between--
I know!
You're not the only one who
can use Observation Haki.
Except my boy's got a long way to go!
He's too panicked!
Still, I appreciate you showing up, Katakuri.
The Navy seems to have their
hands full with the rescue.
Don't suppose I can convince you to settle down?
That must be Luffy.
Shanks!
That worked!
We struck at the same time as in the real world!
Did you just--?!
Three-Swords Style Secret Art!
Crossing the Six Paths!
This isn't getting us anywhere.
I can't believe that crap swordsman
used me for a boost!
I'll get him for that!
We don't have time for this!
Dammit, if we could just do
something about its limbs!
Get it together, Captain Usopp!
In times like this, you gotta keep calm!
Dad?!
Finally noticed, you little knucklehead?
I can see it! I can see what Dad sees!
Luffy!
All right, you guys! Give it all you've got!
Yeah!
All right, men... Give it all you've got!
We've gotta deal with Tot Musica's limbs!
Take the shots as I call them!
Start with the right leg!
Right leg!
Left arm!
Left leg!
I guess we have to!
You people owe me for this!
Middle, on the right!
Middle, on the left!
Yasopp and his boy actually
get along pretty well.
Right arm!
Franky Fresh Fire!
Luffy!
Shanks!
Go for it!
Did you see that? They should've
never picked a fight with us!
I'm glad they did!
This haul will keep us fed for a while!
Treasure for us, treasure for us,
treasure for us, treasure for us!
Where the heck did you come from?
Did those pirates kidnap her from somewhere?
You gotta be kidding me!
Okay, you win! Quiet down! Uh...
Go to sleep, little baby...
Nice and quiet-like!
Maybe this happened for a reason.
What do you know...
I guess you were lonely, too.
Shanks... I...
It's fine! It's over now.
If you drink this and sleep
right away, you'll make it.
Shanks... I didn't wanna see you again.
But... I missed you!
Stop talking! Hurry and drink.
What's going on here?!
I thought beating the Demon King
would bring their souls back!
Stop it...
Stop fighting, please...
Stop!
Why aren't we back yet?! What's going on?!
We were too late.
Our souls were swallowed
by Tot Musica's power.
No!
Uta, hurry up and drink!
I have to sing. I have to bring them all back.
Shanks... remember what you told me?
That my singing... has the power
to make people happy...
I... I'm the musician of the Red-Haired Pirates, Uta!
I recall that day
we played together by the sea
Just you and me
Still that scent of ocean
seems to fade each passing day
It slips away
So I sing an old familar song
I hope you know the one
I will sing to call you back to me
I need you to hear it
Need you to believe in
Something out there beyond the open sea
Out in the starlight
I need you to hear it
Need you to believe in
There's a wind stirring my wings
That is always beckoning
Calling me above into the open sky
The singing voice of an angel... That's Uta.
Tried my best to hear it
Trying to believe in
Something out there beyond the open sea
Out in the starlight
Trying to believe it
I think I believe it
That one day we'll meet again
And continue this dreamland
In the gleaming dawn
we'll wake up once again
Hey, how come you didn't actually hit me?
Didn't I tell you? My punches
hit harder than a pistol.
You used to do it all the time, though.
Those wimpy, spinny punches of yours!
Those weren't for real!
You're being a sore loser again!
I guess you got taller than me
at some point, huh?
This hat means a lot to me, too.
I want you to be a man who's even
more worthy of it someday, okay?
Shanks... Is Luffy...?
He's back.
The entire audience, too.
What a relief...
Sorry. I should've believed in you
and the Red-Haired Pirates.
But... you still came to help me. Thank you.
Now then, how about you hand Uta,
the arch criminal who almost
destroyed the world, over to us?
You people...
I take it you won't cooperate, then?
Everyone...
This girl...
is my daughter.
She's a precious part of our family.
If you wanna take her...
...you'd better be ready to die!
That even took down a handful of vice admirals.
So this is Haki of Shanks,
one of the four Emperors...
Let's stand down.
I'd rather not go to war with
so many civilians around.
Are my fans gonna be okay?
They'll be fine. People aren't that fragile.
Besides... a new age is dawning soon.
Where did it come from?
Where could this wind be taking us?
I look up to the sky hoping for answers
But there is no reply
Where will it end up,
This song that I've been a vessel for?
I look within knowing I'll find the answer
Even on my own
Let's row out to the open sea,
far as we can go
To the unknown
I've got to keep on dreamin'
No surrenderin'
Go on
Hoist the sail inside my open heart
And let me heed the call of the sea
I've got to keep on singin'...
You were asleep for a while.
Where's Uta? And Shanks?
There.
Where did it come from?
Where could this wind be taking us?
I look up to the sky hoping for answers
But there is no reply
Where will it end up,
This song I've been a vessel for?
I look within knowing I'll find the answer
Even on my own
Let's row out to the open sea,
Far as we can go
To the unknown...
I've got to keep on dreamin'
No surrenderin'
Go on
Hoist the sail inside my open heart
And let me heed the call of the sea
I've got to keep on singin'
Until you feel it
Just hold on
Oh, the winds will change, I promise you
My voice will see us through
To the end
All of us searching
Trying to find our happiness
Our hands reach out and all we find is pain
Still we must try again
What if that sorrow
Becomes the strength that we're lookin' for?
Then we can weather any storm that comes
Ready for what's in store
When all is said and done
I hope that we will meet again
At the ending
Let me keep on living this waking dream
There's no waking me
Let's dream on
I see something far ahead of me
A path that's waiting for me
Just beyond
I'll always be here singin'
Until you feel it
Just hold on
Oh, my voice will be the wind that fills
Your sails so you can still
Carry on
I've got to keep on dreamin'
Never surrenderin'
Go on
Oh and even if I disappear
My song will still ring out
For you to hear
I have got to keep on singin'
Want you to feel it
Just hold on
Oh, the winds will change, I promise you
My voice will see us through
To the end
Hey, Sunny!
Sunny?
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!